<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Donate on Brixton Local</title>
    <link>https://tender-bell-527fff.netlify.com/tags/donate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Donate on Brixton Local</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 22:18:39 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tender-bell-527fff.netlify.com/tags/donate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Brixton Soup Kitchen</title>
      <link>https://tender-bell-527fff.netlify.com/posts/brsoup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 22:18:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tender-bell-527fff.netlify.com/posts/brsoup/</guid>
      <description>We are a Brixton based service for the homeless and people in need. However, we help people who are from London and surrounding areas. We rely on donations and volunteers to continue our work.
Brixton Soup Kitchen, founded in 2013 by Solomon Smith and Mahamed Hashi, has become a bastion of community support in the Brixton area, serving free meals twice a day as well as providing a clothing bank, a food bank, free to use computers with internet, and legal advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lambeth Foodbank Fund</title>
      <link>https://tender-bell-527fff.netlify.com/posts/lambethfund/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 22:18:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tender-bell-527fff.netlify.com/posts/lambethfund/</guid>
      <description>The world is experiencing an unprecedented challenge. It is important, in this moment, that we cooperate and do what we can to support one another. The Lambeth Food Bank Fund has launched to support our community and the organisations that can have the most impact on those that are most vulnerable.
The funds will go to the most vulnerable people during this crisis. They will be administered by Holy Trinity Clapham and delivered to food banks across the borough - including Brixton &amp;amp; Norwood, Clapham Park, Vauxhall, and Waterloo - that can help the most vulnerable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Norwood and Brixton Foodbank</title>
      <link>https://tender-bell-527fff.netlify.com/posts/nfoodbank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 22:18:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tender-bell-527fff.netlify.com/posts/nfoodbank/</guid>
      <description>Our foodbank is run by local people for local people – we rely on the community’s support to ensure we can continue to stop people going hungry. Can you invest in the future of our project and help us provide much-needed support to people in crisis in our community?
Giving more than just food Big or small, every gift you give helps transform lives. We couldn’t do what we do without your support.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>